{
    "subject": "resource/Stay_(Faraway,_So_Close!)",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "resource/U2",
    "human_readable": "The artist of Stay (Faraway, So Close!) is U2.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8870031833648682,
            "question": "Are there other popular songs by U2 besides 'Stay (Faraway, So Close!)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8223194479942322,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind the song 'Stay (Faraway, So Close!)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644819974899292,
            "question": "What is the meaning behind the title 'Stay (Faraway, So Close!)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6305422782897949,
            "question": "Which band created the music for 'Stay (Faraway, So Close!)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5859530568122864,
            "question": "When was the song 'Stay (Faraway, So Close!)' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35677412152290344,
            "question": "What is the title of the song performed by U2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3539302349090576,
            "question": "What genre of music is typically associated with U2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2890484631061554,
            "question": "Is U2 known for performing rock music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1413131058216095,
            "question": "Has U2 won any awards for their music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10004757344722748,
            "question": "Name a famous song by U2."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of Stay (Faraway, So Close!) is U2.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3315_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has U2 won any awards for their music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3315_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is U2 known for performing rock music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3315_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is typically associated with U2?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3315_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3315_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to U2's involvement with the song \"Stay (Faraway, So Close!)\", including its inclusion in their album Zooropa and its creation inspired by Wim Wenders' film of the same name. Therefore, the statement that the artist of \"Stay (Faraway, So Close!)\" is U2 is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}